

DHARMAPALA K.H.N.D

A fourth-year undergraduate student at Sri Lanka Institute of Information Technology (SLIIT) reading for BSc Hons Degree in Information Technology specializing in Software Engineering.Possess a strong academic performance along with leadership skills. Ambitious for an internship in the Computing field.

naweendilshan26@gmail.com

- 071-7475188
- Ħ Mar 2, 2000
- Sri lanka
- Delgahaheena watta, Karametiya,

EXPERIENCE

O JAN 2022 - NOV 2022 INTERN SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Mobitel (PVT) LTD. Colombo 00300

O JAN 2023 - PRESENT TRAINEE SOFTWARE ENGINEER

LAKMOBILE TECHNOLOGY SOLUTIONS (PVT) LTD

SKILLS



github / gitlab

EDUCATION

O JAN 2020 - PRESENT BSC HONS IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

SPECIALIZING IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING.

SLIIT

0 2017 - 2019 G.C.E. ADVANCED LEVEL

. H/Walasmulla N.S

Physics C Chemistry S

Combine Mathematics S

U LANGUAGES

English

Sinhala

PROJECTS

ACADENIC PROJECTS

WEB APPLICATION FOR WONDER LANKA TOURIST MANAGEMENT SYSTEM (MONGODB, EXPRESS, REACT, NODEJS)

I and my team has developed a Online Tourist Management System for WonderLanka

(pvt) Company.(Year 2 Semester 2 project)

https://wonderlanka.netlify.app

https://wonderlanka-company-dashboard.netlify.app

Esay_Buy E-commerce Web application

(MONGODB, EXPRESS, REACT, NODEJS)

I developed a Seller Managment both FrontEnd and BackEnd.

PortFolio WebSite (REACT) https://it20207540.github.io/

• CMS Financial Web Application - LAKMOBILE TECHNOLOGY SOLUTIONS (PVT) (SPRINGBOOT, REACT, SQL)

CMS is debt recovery system deployed in debt recovery agents. Companies likes Banks, leasing companies, telecommunication providers outsource their debt collection to 3 rd party debt recovery agents. So these agents collects debt collections from their clients and help to recover the debts.

- SLT-Mobitel C-Panel Project LAKMOBILE TECHNOLOGY SOLUTIONS (PVT) (SPRINGBOOT, REACT, SQL)
- SLT-Mobitel Enterprise Project LAKMOBILE TECHNOLOGY SOLUTIONS (PVT) (SPRING BOOT, REACT, SQL)

REFERENCES

Mr.Lakshan Samarasinghe (Bsc.Software Eng) Associate Tech Lead at Aeturnum0765259277, hklsamarasinghagmail.com

Mr. Upul indrajith (Bsc. Eng, Msc) 0773002076, indrajithy.wcpgmail.com